Guide to the McKim Mead and White Architectural Records circa 1875-1950 PR 42
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Architectural Drawings
  - Subseries I.2: Flat drawings
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Station, New York City, reproductions of station's working drawings (Box Flat files, Folder FF44)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Station in New York City, proposed mural painting (Box Flat files, Folder FF45)
    - Silk Center Building, Inc., drawing 8, roof and tank house plan (linen), 1925 (Box Flat files, Folder FF46)
    - "House A, House B" (Box Flat files, Folder FF47)
    - "House D," 3 drawings (Box Flat files, Folder FF48)
    - "House F," 11 drawings (Box Flat files, Folder FF49)
    - "House G" (Box Flat files, Folder FF50)
    - Early drawings of cottages (Box Flat files, Folder FF51)
    - Sir Ronald Lindsay, full-size details for library/book room (Box Flat files, Folder FF52)
    - Boston Music Hall, Symphony Hall, Boston, plans section and elevation of original design (rejected designs), Plan (neg. 51896), section (neg. 51897) (Box Flat files, Folder FF53)
    - Amherst College Library, Amherst, MA (1968 collection). 4 mounted plans (Box Flat files, Folder FF54)
    - Amherst College Library, Amherst, MA, longitudinal and transverse sections (Box Flat files, Folder FF54A)
    - Pennsylvania Station, Pittsburgh, PA, Lower concourse looking east (Box Flat files, Folder FF55)
    - Pennsylvania Station, Pittsburgh, PA, Upper concourse looking east (Box Flat files, Folder FF55)
    - Middlesex Hospital, Middletown, CT, east elevation (Box Flat files, Folder FF56)
    - Middlesex Hospital, Middletown, CT, west elevation (Box Flat files, Folder FF56)
    - Middlesex Hospital, Middletown, CT, west elevation, 8-story scheme (Box Flat files, Folder FF56)
    - Middlesex Hospital, Middletown, CT, west elevation, 4-story scheme (Box Flat files, Folder FF56)
    - Tennessee Memorial Competition, 2 plans (Box Flat files, Folder FF57)
    - Girard College Chapel Competition, Philadelphia, PA (Box Flat files, Folder FF57)
    - Custom House, competition drawing, New York (Box Flat files, Folder FF57)
    - Miscellaneous houses (Box Flat files, Folder FF58)
    - Country house for Thomas Jefferson Coolidge, esq., Manchester, MA (reproductions; original drawings owned by John Lastavica and Kitty Coolidge) (Box Flat files, Folder FF59)
    - Prospect Park (Box Flat files, Folder FF60)
    - Prospect Park (Box Flat files, Folder FF61)
    - Grand Central Station Competition, ink on trace, perspective from the north (Box Flat files, Folder FF62)
    - Competition for monumental memorial to Theodore Roosevelt (Box Flat files, Folder FF62)
    - Unidentified project, color rendering (Box Flat files, Folder FF62)
    - Unidentified drawing of bridge (Box Flat files, Folder FF63)
    - Unidentified photo/plan (Box Flat files, Folder FF63)
    - NY Central West Side improvement, City Structure No. 4 and Grade Crossing elimination between 72nd and 80th Street, Manhattan (Box Flat files, Folder FF63)
    - New York University, Library Doors in memory of Stanford White (Box Flat files, Folder FF63)
    - Renderings of unidentified buildings (2 by Jules Crow) (Box Flat files, Folder FF64)
    - Bates Hall, Boston Public Library, 1/2 plan, architrave and jamb. Very poor condition. "Restricted. (Box Flat files, Folder FF65)
    - Brooklyn Institute, north elevation (Box Flat files, Folder FF67)
    - San Giorgio dei Schiavi, Venice, Italy, Details of concourse and paneling on walls (Box Flat files, Folder FF67)
    - Cayuga Lake Hotel: view of tower, Interlaken, NY (Box Flat files, Folder FF67)
    - Hotel, Tarrytown Heights, NY (Box Flat files, Folder FF67)
    - Catharine Lorillard Wolfe Residence (proposed), RI (attributed by Leland Roth) (Box Flat files, Folder FF67)
    - Municipal Building, NYC, 2 views by Jules Crow (Box Flat files, Folder FF68)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Garden, Brooklyn, NY (Box Flat files, Folder FF69)
    - State Savings Bank at Detroit, front elevation (Box Flat files, Folder FF70)
    - First National Bank Building, lithograph (poor condition), 1908 (Box Flat files, Folder FF71)
    - Judson Memorial Baptist Church (Box Flat files, Folder FF72)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA, Preliminary study for general plan (very poor condition) (Box Flat files, Folder FF73)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, NYC, Library and gallery (Box Flat files, Folder FF74)
    - National City Bank, Hong Kong branch, plan (Box Flat files, Folder FF75)
    - New York Terminal Station, Pennsylvania Railroad Company (Box Flat files, Folder FF76)
    - Morgan Library (photo) (Box Flat files, Folder FF76)
    - Columbia University dormitories (photograph, poor condition) (Box Flat files, Folder FF77)
    - Hamilton Hall, Columbia University, NYC (Box Flat files, Folder FF77)
    - New York Herald building, NYC (Box Flat files, Folder FF77)
    - Gorham Co. building photograph (Box Flat files, Folder FF77)
    - Gorham Co. building photograph, interior (Box Flat files, Folder FF77)
    - Madison Square Garden, photograph (George P. Hall) (Box Flat files, Folder FF78)
    - City Hall, NYC, photograph (Box Flat files, Folder FF78)
    - Harvard University buildings, 2 photographs (Box Flat files, Folder FF78)
    - Town Hall, NYC, exterior photograph (Box Flat files, Folder FF79)
    - MMW office rules, 1894 (Box Flat files, Folder FF81)
    - French certificate awarded to McKim for 1900 Universal Exposition (Box Flat files, Folder FF81)
    - Pyne Residence, NYC. Floor plans, blueprint, mounted drawing (Box Flat files, Folder FF82)
    - Proposed library, Port Chester, NY (Box Flat files, Folder FF83)
    - Moore Laboratory of Chemistry, Amherst, MA, study for setting for portrait and memorial tablet (Box Flat files, Folder FF83)
    - Davenport Memorial Squash Building, Amherst College, Amherst, MA, south elevation (Box Flat files, Folder FF83)
    - Davenport Memorial Squash Building, Amherst College, Amherst, MA, north elevation (Box Flat files, Folder FF83)
    - Chicago World's Fair buildings (photo, very poor condition) (Box Flat files, Folder FF84)
    - Henry Villard residence (watercolor) (Box Flat files, Folder FF85)
    - Pennsylvania Station, New York City, presentation drawing, Jules Crow (watercolor) (Box Flat files, Folder FF86.1)
    - Pennsylvania Station, New York City, presentation drawing, Jules Crow (watercolor) (Box Flat files, Folder FF86.2)
    - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Box Flat files, Folder FF87)
    - Gould Memorial, entrance doors, photograph (Box Flat files, Folder FF88)
    - John W. Weeks Bridge, Cambridge, MA, photograph (Box Flat files, Folder FF88)
    - United States Post Office, NYC (3 drawings) (Box Flat files, Folder FF89)
    - Winifred Masterson Burke Relief Foundation, White Plains, NY (Box Flat files, Folder FF89)
    - McKinley Birthplace Memorial Competition, front elevation and first floor plan (Box Flat files, Folder FF89)
    - Savoy Plaza Hotel (Box Flat files, Folder FF89)
    - House for L.C. Hanna, Cleveland, OH (Box Flat files, Folder FF89)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Station, NYC, interior photograph (Box Flat files, Folder FF89)
    - Court of the States, 1939 World's Fair, New York, photograph (Box Flat files, Folder FF89)
    - Women's Dormitories South Campus Project (Box Flat files, Folder FF90)
    - Trinity Church, Roslyn, LI. Mounted linen, front elevation (Box Flat files, Folder FF90)
    - Wharton School of Finance and Commerce, main entrance (Box Flat files, Folder FF90)
    - McKinley Birthplace Memorial Competition, front elevation and first floor plan (Box Flat files, Folder FF90)
    - American Military Cemetery, Florence, Italy, prelimary study (Box Flat files, Folder FF90)
    - Princeton University, Field House (Box Flat files, Folder FF90)
    - Bank of Montreal (Wall Street), assorted blueprints (Box Flat files, Folder FF91)
    - Bank of Montreal (Montreal), assorted blueprints; detail drawings of lamps (Box Flat files, Folder FF92)
    - Bank of Montreal (Winnipeg), assorted blueprints (Box Flat files, Folder FF93)
    - Barnard College, structural blueprints (Box Flat files, Folder FF94)
    - Beard Residence, entrance elevation and studies of rooms (Box Flat files, Folder FF95)
    - Bellevue Hospital, blueprints (water main, garage, site plan) (Box Flat files, Folder FF96)
    - Royal Trust Company, drawings on tissue (Box Flat files, Folder FF97)
    - Governors Island Ventilation Building (Box Flat files, Folder FF98)
    - Hotel Pennsylvania Floor Plans (Box Flat files, Folder FF99)
    - Charles Adsitt, Esq. Hornsville, NY. Sketch of house. (Box Flat files, Folder FF 100)
      General Note
      This drawing is signed "McKim Mead and Bigelow"
    - St. Bartholomew's Church. Proposed Doors and Porch, 1902 (Box Flat files, Folder FF 101)
    - Charles H. Williams, Esq. residence, Buffalo, NY, south elevation, 1895 (Box Flat files, Folder FF 102)
    - Goucher College Drawings, 1938 (Box Flat files, Folder FF 103)
    - Municipal Building photo, 1908 (Box Flat files, Folder FF 104)
    - Adelphi College Recreation Building photo (Box Flat files, Folder FF 104)
    - New York Post-Graduate Hospital and Medical School drawing (Box Flat files, Folder FF 104)
    - City Hall, Schenectady, NY (Box Flat files, Folder FF 104)
    - Unidentified buildings - photographs (Box Flat files, Folder FF 105)
- Series II: Correspondence
  This series consists of approximately 665 hollinger boxes of documents -- primarily letters, but also a large amount of billing correspondence and some contracts. The files also occasionally include small drawings, rough sketches, specifications, photographs and clippings. A small amount of additional correspondence may be located in Series III, Specifications.
  - Subseries II.A: 1950 Transfer
    Arrangement
    The subseries is believed to be in its original order as received by N-YHS. It is arranged in alphabetical order by what appears to be client name. Specific files/projects within an overall client name are shown in folder level notes. Project numbers are shown in (parentheses).
    - Adelphi College, Garden City, NY (666) (Box 1 of 5) (Offsite-box II.1)
    - Adelphi College, Garden City, NY (666) (Box 2 of 5) (Offsite-box II.2)
    - Adelphi College, Garden City, NY (666) (Box 3 of 5) (Offsite-box II.3)
    - Adelphi College, Garden City, NY (666) (Box 4 of 5) (Offsite-box II.4)
    - Adelphi College, Garden City, NY (666) (667) (Box 5 of 5) (Offsite-box II.5)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 1 of 14) (Offsite-box II.6)
      Moore Chemistry Building (17 1/2)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 2 of 14) (Offsite-box II.7)
      Moore Chemistry Building (17 1/2, cont'd)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 3 of 14) (Offsite-box II.8)
      Johnson Chapel and Williston and College Halls (18); Church (old) (21); General (22)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 4 of 14) (Offsite-box II.9)
      General (22 cont'd); Union Building (23)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 5 of 14) (Offsite-box II.10)
      Church (new) (20); Observatory (19); General Electric Plant (28-1/2); Library (24)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 6 of 14) (Offsite-box II.11)
      Library (24, cont'd)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 7 of 14) (Offsite-box II.12)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 8 of 14) (Offsite-box II.13)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 9 of 14) (Offsite-box II.14)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 10 of 14) (Offsite-box II.15)
      Library (24, cont'd); Commons (25); Power House (25 1/2)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 11 of 14) (Offsite-box II.16)
      Amherst College and College Hall (625); Johnson Chapel (27); Gymnasium (26)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 12 of 14) (Offsite-box II.17)
      Baseball Cage (26 1/2); Dormitory (27 1/2)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 13 of 14) (Offsite-box II.18)
      Dormitory (27 1/2, cont'd)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA. (Box 14 of 14) (Offsite-box II.19)
      Appleton Hall (28)
    - Bank of Montreal, 68 Wall Street, New York, NY (Box 1 of 4) (Offsite-box II.20)
      68 Wall Street, General (270)
    - Bank of Montreal, 68 Wall Street, New York, NY (Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box II.21)
      68 Wall Street, General (270, cont'd); 64-66 Wall Street Alterations (2)
    - Bank of Montreal, 68 Wall Street, New York, NY (Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box II.22)
      60-68 Wall Street Alterations (306)
    - Bank of Montreal, 68 Wall Street, New York, NY (Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box II.23)
      60-68 Wall Street Alterations (306, cont'd)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Box 1 of 8) (Offsite-box II.23)
      General (307)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Box 2 of 8) (Offsite-box II.24)
      General (308); Royal Trust Co. (309)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Box 3 of 8) (Offsite-box II.25)
      General (608)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Box 4 of 8) (Offsite-box II.26)
      General (608A); Miscellaneous Branch Banks (241)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Box 5 of 8) (Offsite-box II.27)
      Miscellaneous (no #)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Box 6 of 8) (Offsite-box II.28)
      1920 Alterations to Main Building (340)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Box 7 of 8) (Offsite-box II.29)
      1920 Alterations to Main Building (340, cont'd)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Box 8 of 8) (Offsite-box II.30)
      1920 Alterations to Main Building (340, cont'd); see also Box 228
    - Bank of Montreal, Brandtford, Canada (224) (Offsite-box II.30)
    - Bank of Montreal, Winnipeg, Canada (1) (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.31)
    - Bank of Montreal, Winnipeg, Canada (1) (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.32)
    - Barnard College, New York, NY. Dormitory Wing, Brooks Hall Alteration (495) (Box 1 of 4) (Offsite-box II.33)
    - Barnard College, New York, NY. Dormitory Wing, Brooks Hall Alteration (495) (Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box II.34)
    - Barnard College, New York, NY. Dormitory Wing, Brooks Hall Alteration (495) (Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box II.35)
    - Barnard College, New York, NY. Dormitory Wing, Brooks Hall Alteration (495) (Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box II.36)
    - Beard or Lorillard, Tuxedo Park, NY. Residence (664) (Box 1 of 4) (Offsite-box II.37)
    - Beard or Lorillard, Tuxedo Park, NY. Residence (664) (Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box II.38)
    - Beard or Lorillard, Tuxedo Park, NY. Residence (664) (Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box II.39)
    - Beard or Lorillard, Tuxedo Park, NY. Residence (664) (Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box II.40)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. General (47) (Box 1 of 36) (Offsite-box II.41)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. General (47) (Box 2 of 36) (Offsite-box II.42)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. General (47) (Box 3 of 36) (Offsite-box II.43)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. General (47) (Box 4 of 36) (Offsite-box II.44)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilion "A and B" (48) (Box 5 of 36) (Offsite-box II.45)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilion "A and B" (48) (Box 6 of 36) (Offsite-box II.46)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilion "A and B" (48) (Box 7 of 36) (Offsite-box II.47)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilion "A and B" (48) (Box 8 of 36) (Offsite-box II.48)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pathological Department (49) (Box 9 of 36) (Offsite-box II.49)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pathological Department (49) (Box 10 of 36) (Offsite-box II.50)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pathological Department (49) (Box 11 of 36) (Offsite-box II.51)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Laundry Building (50) (Box 12 of 36) (Offsite-box II.52)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Laundry Building (50) (Box 13 of 36) (Offsite-box II.53)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY (Box 14 of 36) (Offsite-box II.54)
      Boiler House and Coaling Station (51)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY (Box 15 of 36) (Offsite-box II.55)
      Boiler House and Coaling Station (51, cont'd); Temp Boiling House (52)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilion "I and K" (53) (Box 16 of 36) (Offsite-box II.56)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY.. Pavilion "I and K" (53) (Box 17 of 36) (Offsite-box II.57)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilion "I and K" (53) (Box 18 of 36) (Offsite-box II.58)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY (Box 19 of 36) (Offsite-box II.59)
      Pavilion "I and K," (cont'd) and "L and M" miscellaneous; Radiographic Department (Pavilions "I and K"); Hydrotherapeutic Department (Pavilions "I and K"); Sun Parlor (Pavilion "I") (all 53)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilion "L and M" (53) (Box 20 of 36) (Offsite-box II.60)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilion "L and M" (53) (Box 21 of 36) (Offsite-box II.61)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilion "L and M" (53) (Box 22 of 36) (Offsite-box II.62)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY (Box 23 of 36) (Offsite-box II.63)
      Alteration to Wards 18, 25, and 31 (54); Tunnel between Pavilion "A and B" to Nurses Home (55); Pavilion "7 and 11" (57); Pavilion for the Insane (58); Pavilion "E and H" (59)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Out Patient Department (56) (Box 24 of 36) (Offsite-box II.64)
    - Bellevue Hospital. New York, NY. Out Patient Department (56) (Box 25 of 36) (Offsite-box II.65)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Out Patient Department (56) (Box 26 of 36) (Offsite-box II.66)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilions "F and G" (60) (Box 27 of 36) (Offsite-box II.67)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilions "F and G" (60) (Box 28 of 36) (Offsite-box II.68)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilions "F and G" (60) (Box 29 of 36) (Offsite-box II.69)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilions "F and G" (60) (Box 30 of 36) (Offsite-box II.70)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilions "F and G" (60) (Box 31 of 36) (Offsite-box II.71)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilions "F and G" (60) (Box 32 of 36) (Offsite-box II.72)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY. Pavilions "F and G" (60) (Box 33 of 36) (Offsite-box II.73)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY (Box 34 of 36) (Offsite-box II.74)
      Nurses Training School (Additional Wings) (63)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY (Box 35 of 36) (Offsite-box II.75)
      Nurses Training School (Additional Wings) (63, cont'd); Alcoholic Ward (64); Old Bldg.—Fire Hazard (65); Ambulance Platform (66 ½); Clinic (67)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY (Box 36 of 36) (Offsite-box II.76)
      Garage (66)
    - Bliss, Robert W., Washington, D.C. (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.77)
      Residence, general (396)
    - Bliss, Robert W., Washington, D.C. (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.78)
    - Boston Public Library, Boston, MA (Box 1 of 3) (Offsite-box II.79)
      General (101)
    - Boston Public Library, Boston, MA (Box 2 of 3) (Offsite-box II.80)
      General (102)
    - Boston Public Library, Boston, MA (Box 3 of 3) (Offsite-box II.81)
      General (103)
    - Breese, James. L., Southampton, NY (Offsite-box II.82)
      Residence (570)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Gardens, Brooklyn, NY (Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box II.83)
      General (43)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Gardens, Brooklyn, NY (Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box II.84)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Gardens, Brooklyn, NY (Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box II.85)
      General (43 1/2)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Gardens, Brooklyn, NY (Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box II.86)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Gardens, Brooklyn, NY (Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box II.87)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Gardens, Brooklyn, NY (Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box II.88)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 1 of 17) (Offsite-box II.89)
      General (6)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 2 of 17) (Offsite-box II.90)
      General (6), cont'd
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 3 of 17) (Offsite-box II.91)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 4 of 17) (Offsite-box II.92)
      West Wing (37); Temporary Office Building (38); Central Pavilion and Approach (39); Astronomical Observatory (41); Power House (42)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 5 of 17) (Offsite-box II.93)
      East Wing (40)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 6 of 17) (Offsite-box II.94)
      Wings F and G (44)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 7 of 17) (Offsite-box II.95)
      Wings F and G (44), cont'd
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 8 of 17) (Offsite-box II.96)
      Wings F and G (44 1/2)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 9 of 17) (Offsite-box II.97)
      Wings F and G (44 1/2), cont'd
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 10 of 17) (Offsite-box II.98)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 11 of 17) (Offsite-box II.99)
      Children's Garden House (45); Wood, Metal and Exhibition Case (46); Candelabra and Bronze Works (46); Counters and Bulletin Boards (46)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 12 of 17) (Offsite-box II.100)
      Watchman's Night Lighting System (46); Elevator Additions (46); General (182)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 13 of 17) (Offsite-box II.101)
      First Section (205); First Section (206)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 14 of 17) (Offsite-box II.102)
      General (405); General (406)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 15 of 17) (Offsite-box II.103)
      General (489)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 16 of 17) (Offsite-box II.104)
      General (490)
    - Brooklyn Institute, Brooklyn, NY (Box 17 of 17) (Offsite-box II.105)
      General (491)
    - City Hall, Burlington, VT (Box 1 of 3) (Offsite-box II.106)
      General (588)
    - City Hall, Burlington, VT (Box 2 of 3) (Offsite-box II.107)
    - City Hall, Burlington, VT (Box 3 of 3) (Offsite-box II.108)
    - Carnegie Libraries, New York, NY? (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.109)
      General (575)
    - Carnegie Libraries, New York, NY? (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.110)
      General (576)
    - Cheney, Anne W., South Manchester, CT (Offsite-box II.111)
      Residence (593)
    - Century Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.112)
      General (37)
    - Colony Club, New York, NY (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.113)
      General (590)
    - Colony Club, New York, NY (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.114)
      General (591)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 1 of 81) (Offsite-box II.115)
      Kent Hall (69)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 2 of 81) (Offsite-box II.116)
      Kent Hall (69), cont'd
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 3 of 81) (Offsite-box II.117)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 4 of 81) (Offsite-box II.118)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 5 of 81) (Offsite-box II.119)
      General (70); Lecture Hall (71)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 6 of 81) (Offsite-box II.120)
      Philosophy Building (72)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 7 of 81) (Offsite-box II.121)
      Philosophy Building (72), cont'd
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 8 of 81) (Offsite-box II.122)
      McKim Memorial Tablet (73); Sun Dial and Widening of 116 St. (74)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 9 of 81) (Offsite-box II.123)
      Avery Building (75)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 10 of 81) (Offsite-box II.124)
      Avery Building (75), cont'd
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 11 of 81) (Offsite-box II.125)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 12 of 81) (Offsite-box II.126)
      Miscellaneous Memorials (76)
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 13 of 81) (Offsite-box II.127)
      Miscellaneous Memorials (76), cont'd
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 14 of 81) (Offsite-box II.128)
      New Lecture Hall (Physics Bldg) (77); Alteration to Fayerweather Hall (77); Posts of Gateway (78)